Console Wars is a documentary film directed by Blake J. Harris.
In 1990, SEGA, a fledgling arcade company assembled a team of misfits to take
on the greatest video game company in the world, Nintendo.
It was a once-in-a-lifetime, no-holds-barred conflict that pit brother against brother, kids against grownups,
Sonic against Mario, and uniquely American capitalism against centuries-old Japanese tradition.
For the first time ever, the men and women who fought on the front lines for
Sega and Nintendo discuss this battle that defined a generation.
Self, played by Howard Phillips.
Self, played by Shinobu Toyoda.
Self, played by Paul Rioux.
Self, played by Tom Kalinske.
Self, played by Gail Tilden.
Self, played by Peter Main.
Console Wars is a 2020 documentary film directed by Jonah Tulis and Blake J.
Harris, exploring the 1990s console wars between Nintendo and Sega
and Sega's rise and fall in the home console market.
Based on Harris's 2014 book Console Wars, it was the first original
film for CBS All Access, which became Paramount+.
The film explores themes of video game, commercial,
nintendo, based on true story, marketing.